RIJEN MAHARJAN

9813566480



rijen.maharjan1234@gmail.com



Nakkhu, Lalitpur



SKILLS

- HTML, CSS
- Javascript
- Basic React is
- Android
- Basic Python
- Basic PHP Laravel
- Basic MS-office application skills
- Project Management
- Interpersonal Communication skill

EDUCATION

MASTER OF BUSINESS **ADMINISTRATION**

School of Management - Tribhuvan University

2021-23

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

The British College 2016-2020

HIGHER SECONDARY

IdeaL Model Higher Secondary School

2014-2016

SLC

Future Star Higher Secondary School

2014

PROFILE

Open to learning personality with enthusiasm to improve my skills and better my qualities by grasping as much knowledge and experience as possible while contributing to the growth of the organization simultaneously. Team player with an eye for detail.

EXPERIENCE

OPERATIONAL HEAD

Fotoyala, Kupondole

2018 - Present

- Company's front face.
- · Lead generating
- · Photography, Videography and Editing.
- Team building and coordination.

CUSTOMER SERVICE

Troika International Pvt Ltd., Nakhu

2017 - 2018

- Client Support
- · Complaint and queries handling
- Involvement in Marketing Strategies and Planning.
- Handle vendors and suppliers

TRAININGS

- Participated in seminar- "New Venture and Market Creation"
- Python course
- · Graphic designing course
- Remarkable contribution as Community Service Director of Rotaract Club of Jawalakhel Manjushree in RY 2020-21.

PROJECTS

- MBA Live Project Mega Bank
- Mega Projects for different reputed companies.
 - Bhatbhateni
 - Pepe pizza
 - Skechers
 - BYD
- Surkhet Development & Awareness
 Program -Surkhet Municipality
 Documentary Projection
- Covid-19 Awareness Program -Ministry of Health and Population Awareness and Precautionary video projection
- Android Application development

 Final year Project
- Website development PHP laravel

AWARDS

- Best Project Award Live Project
- Project Management
- SLC topper- Locality
- School President- Future Stars High School (2013)

LANGUAGE

- English
- Nepali
- Newari
- Hindi